Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure...
Hey, old man. Something's off.
You're going the wrong direction.
Hmm?
We seem to be heading toward that island.
But before we arrive in Egypt,
we need to make a slight detour.
Someone is waiting for us on the island.
Hmm.
He's a man who is extremely
important to our journey.
What is that supposed to mean?
Hey, what's the big idea?
Does someone actually live here?
This is such a tiny little
island, it's practically deserted.
I would have to agree.
Mr.
Joestar, are you sure
someone actually lives here?
He's been living on
this island by himself.
A man told me back in India, and
I'm sure I heard him correctly.
Wait a sec.
When you say, a man... What?
Mangoes from India?
I
don't
know.
I hate to interrupt,
but I thought you should know someone's
watching us from the grass over there.
What?
Hey!
From the back, he looks...
You're right.
I know that face.
Hold on!
Just wait!
Eat up now!
Are you hungry, Michael?
How about you, Prince?
I mixed in those shells you love, so make
sure you share with the others, alright?
And there's lots more
where this came from.
Make sure to get nice and fat so
you'll be a tasty chicken, Lionel.
It's not possible.
That man...
It can't be. It's... Hold it!
I'm gonna go and talk to him.
The rest of you just wait here for now.
Pardon me, my name is Joseph Joestar.
My friends and I are currently
traveling on an expedition to Egypt...
Go away!
I won't hear it!
His voice sounds like...
I won't say it again!
Don't talk to me!
Got it?
No one ever comes to see me when
they have actual good news to report.
I only get visitors when
something bad happens!
Just shut up!
Go away!
Mr. Avdol!
Avdol, wait! I said go!
Hold on!
That's impossible!
That wasn't Avdol.
It was his father.
His father?
He withdrew from society and
lives alone on this island.
I'm sorry that I wasn't able
to tell you about this earlier.
But if it ever became known to
Dio that we stopped at this place,
Avdahl's father would
be put in grave danger.
I would never forgive
myself if that happened.
But for now, my focus has to be on
telling him what every parent fears most.
That his son is dead.
Pull the rift!
Don't let yourself go there.
Avdol's death wasn't your fault.
No, it's entirely my fault.
I'll carry that burden
for as long as I live.
Is it safe to assume his
father's a stand user?
Yeah, but I don't know what kind of stand
it is or what sort of power it wields.
Judging by the way his
father reacted to us,
I doubt he'll offer us much
in the way of assistance.
You just leave the
talking to me, all right?
Hopefully my words will
be able to reach him.
All I ever wanted was to avenge my sister's
death, and I ended up killing my friend.
There's nothing I could possibly
do to make it up to his father.
I'm between a rock and a hard place.
Talk about depressing.
Huh?
This thing is pretty shiny.
I wonder if it drifted
up from some sunken ship.
Just look at all those barnacles.
It's definitely made of metal, but...
There's some kind of
creepy face carved on it.
Despite that, it looks pretty valuable.
Now if I can scratch off these
barnacles, we'll really be in business.
What the hell?
It's gone!
What in the world happened just now?
From the looks of it,
the air trapped inside just burst
out and I was scared over nothing.
Ooh.
Luckily, I'm not dealing with
Aladdin's magic lamp or anything,
so I guess I can relax a little.
You get three!
Three, I say!
Your wish is my command!
Three wishes for whatever
your heart desires!
What sort of fresh hell is this?
I am known as Cameo.
Allow me to thank you for
freeing me from the lab.
Tell me your three wishes so
that I might grant them for you.
Hold it, you smoky freak!
Are you a new stand user?
Silver Chariots!
Damn it.
This guy's not half bad.
What awesome power!
Listen buddy, your strength tells me
that your user is definitely nearby.
Now who is it?
Would you like the answer to that question
to be considered as your
first official wish?
It's a little on the
boring side if you ask me.
Don't pull that genie in a
bottle crap with me, fishier.
But if you're saying you could make me
a super rich man right this instant,
let's see it.
Is that your first wish?
Going once.
Go ahead and grant it if you can, but
otherwise stop jerking me around, dammit!
Then consider your wish granted. Huh?
Hail to you!
I don't understand a single
thing that just happened.
So that strange guy wasn't
the enemy's stand after all.
I thought he'd attack me, but instead
he told me to make three wishes.
I don't know what's going on
here, but I don't trust that guy.
Someone shady is on this island.
It's probably a good idea to tell Mr.
Joestar what happened here.
There might be a chance it could have
something to do with Avdol's father.
Huh?
That's weird.
What's up with all that
loud clanging back there?
Whoa, is this for real?
But it can't be!
Wait, this is gold from
the Napoleonic era!
This isn't a dream or an illusion!
Holy crap!
A treasure Drive of gold!
I wouldn't believe it
if it wasn't right here!
I don't get it! What is this?
Are you mocking me or something?
No, that's not it.
He can't be mocking me.
When could he have buried this gold here?
There's no way he would have had
time to bury it after I made my wish.
So how the hell did
that freak do all this?
Now, what is your second wish?
Your wish is my command.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why are you doing this?
What are you scheming?
You don't think I'd fall
for your stupid tricks.
If you are my enemy,
then fight me like one.
If not, I'll take this
treasure for myself.
So I take it knowing the answer to
that question is your second wish.
Though it's a little on the
boring side if you ask me,
but I owe you a debt of gratitude
for letting me out of that lamp,
so I shall grant your wish.
You know you're a smug bastard.
All right then, have it your way.
I do have a wish.
I want to be a comic artist!
That was always my dream
back when I was a kid.
And don't make me some
pathetic one either!
I want to be bigger than Disney!
In fact, someday I'm gonna
build my own Polnareff land!
Y-you know what?
Scratch that idea.
Just give me a second to think.
Any minute now, it'll come to me...
I've made up my mind!
I want a beautiful girlfriend!
More than money or fame.
What I want is true love!
I'm talking not only
someone who's really cute!
But a girl who wore pinkies for her?
she loves me with all her heart.
I want to meet a girl who feels the
same way about me as I do for her.
So if that's within your power to do,
then prove it to me right now, dammit!
You want a girl, do you? Very well.
Wait, no, never mind.
I need time to think this through.
I have a question.
Do you have the ability to revive someone?
Am I to assume you're wanting to know the
answer to that question
is your second wish?
Cut it out!
I'm asking you to bring my
dead sister back to life.
And while you're at it, you can
do the same for my friend Avdol.
That shouldn't be too much
of a challenge, right?
Very well.
I shall grant your wish.
Are you serious?
So you can really... do it? Indeed.
But know that since you made two wishes,
I'll grant them in the order you asked.
First, I will grant your second
wish to bring back your sister.
Hail to you!
Hey!
Don't just disappear!
Who the hell are you and
why are you even doing this?
What was that sound?
I'm sure I heard
something rustling around.
It sounded like someone
was digging up the ground.
There's that weird digging again.
Where's that sound coming from?
No, impossible.
Wait, is that a woman crying?
All right, who the hell's back here?
These are...
These are strands of hair,
and a woman's hair no less.
A woman's footsteps.
It can't be!
There's no way this can't
be happening, can it?
As far as I know,
my little sister is still in her coffin
back in France, so how could she be?
Just who the hell are you?
You better answer me right now!
Please, stay away.
I'm in so much pain.
My body hasn't fully formed yet.
I know that voice.
Sherry, it's you.
Polnareff's been gone a while.
Where'd he run off to?
I couldn't find him up top.
Where could he have gone?
It's already nightfall and
he's nowhere to be seen.
Do you think that he could have gotten
tangled up in a fight with the enemy?
Sherry, am I hallucinating
or is it really you?
It is you, isn't it?
Wait!
Where are you going?
Where are you going, Cherry?
Wait, Cherry, it's only me!
Cherry, why are you running away?
Where are you?
Come on, Cherry, please!
I'm begging you to show yourself!
Let me see your face!
Let me see it one more time!
Hey, brother!
Higher, brother!
Raise me as high as you can!
Yay!
Now spin me around!
Oh, it's simply wonderful!
I've been wanting a new umbrella!
Thank you for buying it for me!
I'm off now.
Sherry!
Monkyu, what the hell happened here?
They've been half eaten.
Sherry!
Can you hear me?
Why are you running away?
It's me, your big brother!
Because my body is covered in mud.
And there's my hair.
It's so unkempt.
It's okay, Sherry.
Don't worry about that.
You've got to believe me when I
say you're perfect as you are.
Why are you crying?
Sherry, talk to me.
Why are you sad?
Oh, Sherry.
No.
Just stay back.
Don't come any closer.
What are you saying?
You're not making any sense.
It's simple.
I'm saying you'll hate me.
Oh, Sherry, have I ever said anything
to make you think I'd hate you?
Yes, you have.
It was when we were little kids and I gave
your favorite tropical
fish to that stupid cat.
You got really angry over
it and said you hated me.
I admit I was angry that
day, but no matter what,
I've always loved you more
than the stars in the sky,
and I still do.
Really?
You've always loved me,
no matter what I did?
Yes, of course I have.
And does that feeling
hold true to this day?
I will always love you, no matter what.
And I can clearly see now
that you're the real Sherry.
You have no idea how much I've
missed you, little sister.
I see.
I feel the same, big brother.
Sherry, please look this way.
I'm begging you to show me
that beautiful face of yours.
Why are you crying, Cherry?
Are you still sad? Sad?
No, brother.
These are tears of sadness.
I'm crying because...
What? What is it then?
I'm...
I'm happy, brother.
Cause I can finally hit you!
Ch-Cherry Dunn!
Ch-Cherry...
I'm sorry that I bit you, brother.
I'm afraid my body is
still underdeveloped.
But if I eat your flesh,
I'll return to normal.
It's okay if I eat you, right?
What am I saying?
You always did what I asked you to.
Cameo!
You rang?
You bastard!
What's all the fuss about?
Do you have a complaint?
I granted your wish, didn't I?
Granting wishes is my power after all.
What you do with them
is completely up to you.
Then let me use this opportunity
to tell you my third wish.
Make my sister.
Make her.
Make my sister return to her
grave so she can rest in peace!
I don't think so.
Why not?
You still don't get it, do you, Polnareff?
If you haven't figured
it out, I'm a stand.
Not just any stand.
The one represented by the judgment card.
You see,
my powers allow me to extract wishes from
the deepest corners of the human mind.
and manifest it from the soil below.
You created your sister
from your own yearning.
How dare you?
And since you created
her, I cannot undo it.
It looks like the winner
of this battle is me.
By the way, I seem to recall you
saying something about a third wish.
But don't you remember, Polnareff?
You've already made
your third wish. Oh, no.
You don't mean him.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses.
Take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop, you drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say. Walk
like
an Egyptian.
When a man uncovers his deepest desires.
All of his weaknesses are laid bare.
Because of your idiotic, bumbling eye!
After all, I truly didn't
think you'd be this hurt.
I'll get better if I eat, right?
I know it was only the third wish.